To Do:

Orb Match Page
✓Maybe make a button to link to enemy page. Gotta figure out how to link shit.

Enemy Page
✓add defense break (Radiogroup or dropdown menu)
✓gravity scrolling buttons (for smaller devices)
✓ Show hide gravity list and buttons
✓element reduction (Selections)
✓damage absorbtion over X damage (like sopdet) (EditText)
✓element absorb (Selections? Can there be more than 1?)
✓Coding for setting enemy element
✓Coding for element absorb
✓Coding for element reduction
✓Coding for damage threshold
✓set up fragments with the buttons and adapter
X apply button = takes all the gravity and adjust the current hp of the enemy
	-now applies automatically. Added a clear button instead.
-Need to add that unfocus when keyboard hidden shit as well.
-Need to make sure we get everything into calculations later. Basic functions work. Need calculations.

Calculations Page
✓Make it
Percent damage of monsters
Add total damage of monsters
Subtract target life
maybe make monster damage a dialog fragment to see everything at once
recalculate needs to refresh the page with the additional combos
Figure out color scheme for elements and stuff.

Monster Page
-unfocus when keyboard is hidden (when pressing back) google search : handling back button in keyboard android
-Latent awakenings when they come/translated.

Maybe
-tank calculator
-poison orbs
-Jammer orbs
Stam Calculator